<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1 http://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.1/eml.xsd"
        packageId="10.15468/dl.s52meh"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
  xml:lang="en">

<dataset>
        <alternateIdentifier>0205255-200613084148143</alternateIdentifier>
    <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.s52meh</title>
    <creator>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </creator>
    <metadataProvider>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </metadataProvider>
      <pubDate>
      2021-03-03
      </pubDate>
    <language>ENGLISH</language>
    <abstract>
        <para>A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  &quot;and&quot; : [
    &quot;Continent is Africa&quot;,
    {
      &quot;or&quot; : [
        &quot;Country is Benin&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Burkina Faso&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Cabo Verde&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Côte d’Ivoire&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Gambia&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Ghana&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Guinea&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Guinea-Bissau&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Liberia&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Mali&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Mauritania&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Niger&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Nigeria&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Senegal&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Sierra Leone&quot;,
        &quot;Country is Togo&quot;
      ]
    },
    {
      &quot;or&quot; : [
        &quot;TaxonKey is Rodentia&quot;,
        &quot;TaxonKey is Soricidae&quot;
      ]
    }
  ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
1 records from Collection of  occurrence data on animal species in  the Biosphere Reserve of Pendjari in 2001, 2004, and 2013.
1 records from Lund Museum of Zoology (MZLU)
1 records from California State University, Long Beach Mammals
1 records from Museo Argentino de Ciencias Naturales &quot;Bernardino Rivadavia&quot; (MACN). Mammalogy National Collection (MACNMa)
1 records from Census of animal species in Biosphere Reserve of Pendjari. Data mobilzed in the framework of JRS Biodiversity Foundation funded project in Benin
1 records from UMZC Zoological Specimens
1 records from Museu de Ciències Naturals de Barcelona: MCNB-Cord
2 records from UWBM Mammalogy Collection (Arctos)
2 records from TTU Mammals Collection
2 records from Animal Collections Of The Department of Zoology- Nasarawa State University Keffi
2 records from Inventaire faunique dans le cadre de l&apos;Etude socio-économique de référence des possibilités de valorisation durable des produits forestiers non ligneux dans les réserves de faune de la pendjari
2 records from Pedestrian mammals census in W National Park
3 records from KUBI Mammalogy Collection
3 records from NMNH_material_samples
4 records from Occurrences de vecteurs de maladies recensées à l&apos;Hôpital de Mènontin
4 records from Mammal osteology MZS
5 records from UCM Mammal Collection (Arctos)
5 records from Natural History Museum Rotterdam - Specimens
6 records from CMNH Mammals
7 records from List of animal species censused during activities of ODDB NGO in Benin
7 records from Sapo National Park Bio-monitoring Data
8 records from CRCM Vertebrate Collection
9 records from Biodiversity Research and Teaching Collections - TCWC Vertebrates
9 records from Census of plant and animal species in sacred forests of RAMSAR sites 1017 and 1018 in Benin
10 records from Vertebrate Zoology Division - Mammalogy, Yale Peabody Museum
10 records from Macaulay Library Audio and Video Collection
12 records from UAZ Mammals
12 records from University of Michigan Museum of Zoology, Division of Mammals
15 records from Liste d&apos;espèces animales recensées au cours des activités de l&apos;Organisation pour le Développement Durable et la Biodiversité (ODDB ONG) au Bénin
15 records from Mammifères: Etude d&apos;état initial de la biodiversité dans la concession minière de Guinea Alumina Corporation(GAC) dans la region de Boké (CESP2016-022)
20 records from MSU Mammalogy, Ornithology and Vertebrate Paleontology Collections
26 records from Monitoring of willdife in Benin protected areas
30 records from Paleobiology Database
36 records from UF Florida Museum of Natural History Mammals
68 records from Census of the species of Benin. Data mobilized in the framework of JRS Benin project and funded by JRS Biodiversity Foundation
72 records from IICT Colecção Zoológica
73 records from LACM Vertebrate Collection
129 records from Census of the threatened species of Benin.
147 records from MVZ Mammal Collection (Arctos)
183 records from Observation.org, Nature data from around the World
242 records from Museum of Comparative Zoology, Harvard University
258 records from List of animalia, fungi and plant species recorded through naturalist observations and research activities in Benin. Data mobilized in the framework of a JRS Biodiversity Foundation project of Benin
259 records from Census of animal of Benin: Database 1
261 records from Mammalogy Collection - Royal Ontario Museum
371 records from AMNH Mammal Collections
486 records from Vertebrate observation dataset of North and West Africa (CIBIO-Biodeserts)
682 records from Field Museum of Natural History (Zoology) Mammal Collection
1109 records from Inventaire des espèces animales présentes dans les aires protégées et parcs nationaux au Bénin
1573 records from MSB Mammal Collection (Arctos)
1782 records from Census of the animals of Benin
5042 records from Natural History Museum (London) Collection Specimens
15305 records from African Mammalia
19692 records from The mammals collection (ZM) of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
23268 records from NMNH Extant Specimen Records
</para>
    </abstract>
      <contact>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>      </contact>

</dataset>

<additionalMetadata>
    <metadata>
      <gbif>
        <dateStamp>2021-03-03T11:32:57Z</dateStamp>
      <citation identifier="10.15468/dl.s52meh">GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.s52meh</citation>
              <physical>
                  <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                  <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                  <dataFormat>
                      <externallyDefinedFormat>
                          <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                      </externallyDefinedFormat>
                  </dataFormat>
                  <distribution>
                      <online>
                          <url function="download">https://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0205255-200613084148143.zip</url>
                      </online>
                  </distribution>
              </physical>
        </gbif>
    </metadata>
</additionalMetadata>

</eml:eml>
